[
  {
    "tag": ["water", "health"],
    "question": "drink water / good health",
    "answer": "I think that drinking enough water is good for health."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["in-my-opinion"],
    "question": "bonus good / outstanding employee",
    "answer": "In my opinion, bonuses are effective rewards for outstanding employees."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["i-agree"],
    "question": "creativity / painter",
    "answer": "I agree that creativity is the most important quality for a painter."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["i-agree"],
    "question": "children / advice / parent",
    "answer": "I agree that children need to get advice from their parents."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["i-agree"],
    "question": "students / mobile phones / classroom",
    "answer": "I disagree that students shouldn't be allowed to have mobile phones in the classroom."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["i-agree"],
    "question": "studying abroad / young age",
    "answer": "I disagree that studying abroad at a young age is good."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["i-agree", "cloth"],
    "question": "buying cloth / shop",
    "answer": "I prefer buying my clothes in a shop to shopping on the Internet."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["prefer", "working"],
    "question": "working at office / working at home",
    "answer": "I prefer working at an office rather than working at home."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["better", "learn", "book"],
    "question": "learn from a teacher / learn in a book",
    "answer": "It is better to learn from a teacher than to learn something in a book."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["better", "attend lecture", "study at home"],
    "question": "learn from a teacher / learn in a book",
    "answer": "It is better to attend lectures than to study alone at home."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["think", "small famliy", "large family"],
    "question": "small family / large family",
    "answer": "I think having a small family is better than having a large family."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["living alone", "roommates"],
    "question": "living alone / rommates",
    "answer": "I believe living alone is better than living with roommates."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["tution", "expensive"],
    "question": "tuition fee / expensive",
    "answer": "That’s because tuition fee is too expensive."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["learn", "mistakes"],
    "question": "learn / mistakes",
    "answer": "The reason is that people learn by making mistakes."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["save", "time"],
    "question": "save commuting time",
    "answer": "The reason is that you can save commuting time."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["bicycle", "environment"],
    "question": "riding bicycle / good environment",
    "answer": "First of all, riding a bicycle is good for the environment."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["education", "students"],
    "question": "quality education / student",
    "answer": "First of all, providing quality education for students is important."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["leader", "personality"],
    "question": "good leader / attractive personality",
    "answer": "Secondly, a good leader must have an attractive personality."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["health"],
    "question": "exercising / health",
    "answer": "Secondly, exercising regularly is good for health."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["time"],
    "question": "time / TV at home",
    "answer": "Finally, people don’t have enough time to watch TV at home."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["lecutres"],
    "question": "reviewing / important / lectures",
    "answer": "Finally, reviewing is important to fully understand the lectures."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["child", "bed"],
    "question": "child / bed / ten o'clock",
    "answer": "For example, when I was a child I always went to bed by ten o’clock."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["visited"],
    "question": "Holland / cool",
    "answer": "For example, I recently visited Holland and it was very cool!"
  },
  {
    "tag": ["people"],
    "question": "people need / relax",
    "answer": "To be specific, people need a place to relax."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["bike"],
    "question": "impressive / bikes / cars",
    "answer": "To be specific, it was impressive that there were more bikes than cars."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["fine", "recycling"],
    "question": "people / fine / recycling",
    "answer": "I think people should pay a fine for not recycling."
  },
  {
    "tag": ["food"],
    "question": "food / cook home / restaurants",
    "answer": "Food cooked at home is better than food served at restaurants."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "education / free",
    "answer": "In my opinion, all education should be free."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "prefer / public transportation / car",
    "answer": "I prefer taking public transportation to driving a car."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "children and senior citizens / public transportation",
    "answer": "I disagree children and senior citizens shouldn't have to pay to use public transportation."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "people / equally / benefits / young or old",
    "answer": "First of all, all people should be treated equally. A person should not receive benefits simply because they are young or old."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "save money / public transportation",
    "answer": "I can save money by using public transportation."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "online shopping / save money",
    "answer": "Online shopping helps me save a lot of money."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "exercising regularly / healthy",
    "answer": "Exercising regularly helps me stay healthy."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "healthy / vitamin C / every day",
    "answer": "I can stay healthy by taking vitamin C every day."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "traveling overseas / new experiences",
    "answer": "Traveling overseas gives people a chance to have new experiences."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "experience / broad / perspective",
    "answer": "Having a new experience is important to broaden my perspectives."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "information / newspaper / online reivews",
    "answer": "The information in newspapers is more reliable than online reviews."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "customer reviews / advertisement",
    "answer": "Customer reviews are more reliable than advertisement."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "parents / their children / making mistakes",
    "answer": "Parents give suggestions to their children to prevent them from making mistakes."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "mistake / start over",
    "answer": "If you make a mistake, just erase it and start over."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "cities / activities / residents",
    "answer": "Cities offer a wide range of activities for residents."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "offer / services / cusotmers",
    "answer": "They offer a wide range of services for their customers."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "prefer / advice / colleague / important decision",
    "answer": "I prefer asking a colleague for advice when I have to make an important decision."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "make / quick decision",
    "answer": "I prefer to make a quick decision."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "working abroad / develop career",
    "answer": "Working abroad is a good way to develop one’s career."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "my career / many projects",
    "answer": "I can develop my career by working on many kinds of projects."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "speak manager / deal / probolem at work",
    "answer": "I usually speak with my manager when I need to deal with a problem at work."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "dealing with problem / advice / my parents",
    "answer": "When dealing with a problem, I need some advice from my parents."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "like my job / not stress",
    "answer": "I really like my job because I don’t feel stressed at work."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "stress work / home",
    "answer": "I feel stressed at work because I can’t go home on time."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "working team / myself",
    "answer": "I prefer working with a team to working by myself."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "working team / my career",
    "answer": "Working with a team is good to develop my career."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "earning money / gurantee / happy",
    "answer": "Earning a lot of money does not guarantee a person will be happy."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "earn money / tuition fee",
    "answer": "I need to earn money to pay my tuition fee."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "students / focus / study",
    "answer": "High school students should focus on studying."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "turn off / phone / fstudying",
    "answer": "I always turn my phone off to focus on studying."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "art galleries / studnets / learn art",
    "answer": "Visiting art galleries gives students extra opportunities to learn about art."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "professor / oprrotunity / retake exam",
    "answer": "The professor gave me an opportunity to retake the exam."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "students / interact / community",
    "answer": "It is important for students to interact with members of the community."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "not enjoy / interact / many people",
    "answer": "I don’t enjoy interacting with many people."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "young people / learn / solve problem / own",
    "answer": "I think young people must learn how to solve problems on their own."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "overcome failure / important / life",
    "answer": "Learning how to overcome failures is important in life."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "students / wear uniform",
    "answer": "Many students are required to wear uniforms."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "students / require / final exam",
    "answer": "Students are required to take final exams."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "students / group / good grade",
    "answer": "Students who attend a study group get good grades."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "review / important / grades",
    "answer": "Reviewing is important to get good grades."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "speak another language / undestand / different culture",
    "answer": "Learn how to speak another language allows people to understand different cultures."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "save money / cooking / home",
    "answer": "People can save money by cooking at home."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "working / team / different point of view",
    "answer": "I prefer to working with a team as it helps me get different points of view."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "one's career / internship",
    "answer": "People can develop one's career by doing an internship."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "people / mistake / learn",
    "answer": "When people make a mistake, they learn not to do the same thing again."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "volunteer / new experience",
    "answer": "Joining a volunteer group is a good way to have new experiences."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "Some people like taking vacations in the countryside. Other people enjoy going to a large city on vacation. Which do you prefer and why?",
    "answer": "I enjoy going to a large city on vacation. I have some reasons. Okay, firstly it is obvious that I can meet various people and learn about society. I can learn how to deal with others. There will be a lot of new opportunities to explore more. It is very essential for a young person like me. And um~ I can have more fun, because there are a wide range of food, shops, and activities. Let me tell you my story, because it will be more effective. When I traveled northern part of Canada, the nature was beautiful. But I was very bored. That’s it."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree with the following statement? Parents should always give their children advice or suggestions. Use specific reasons and details to support your opinion.",
    "answer": "I agree that parents should always give their children advice or suggestions. I have some reasons. Okay, firstly it is obvious that children are immature and most are out of control. They do not know what is right and what is wrong! One thing is for sure, most children dislike studying and don't make the right decisions. So, parents must teach and take care of their children. Let me tell you my story, because it will be more effective. When I was a high school student, my parents were very strict. Because of this, I was a good student. That’s it."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "What are the advantages of starting your own company instead of being employed by a company? Use specific ideas and examples to support your opinion.",
    "answer": "There are some advantages of starting my own company. I have some reasons. Okay, firstly it is obvious that I will work harder, and it is possible to earn a lot of money. The second point is that I can have flexible schedules, and do whatever I want. Let me tell you a story, because it will be more effective. I have a friend and he is running a small store. He told me that his life is very busy, but he is proud of himself, and he earned a lot of money. That’s it."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree with the following statement? Social media has improved communication between people. Use specific ideas and examples to support your opinion.",
    "answer": "I agree that social media has improved communication between people. I have some reasons. First, people share their pictures and life stories through social media. I can share my life with people around the world. The second point is that it allows free and real­ time communication. There is no delay and no fee. Let me tell you a story, because it will be more effective. I have a friend and she is living in Canada. We always chat on “SNAPCHAT” all times. I can’t meet her in person, but we share our life online. That’s it."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "Some people prefer to work alone at home, and others prefer to work with a team in an office. Which do you prefer and why? Use specific reasons and details to support your opinion.",
    "answer": "I prefer to work with a team in an office. I have some reasons. Firstly, it is obvious that I can communicate effectively with my co-workers. By communicating, we can understand each other's differences and solve problems quickly. In addition, people can get closer to one another and can achieve better results. Second, I am lazy. Let me tell you a story, because it will be more effective. When I was an intern, I worked at home twice a week. That time, I didn’t work hard. That’s it. "
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "What are the advantages of being able to cook? Give specific reasons and examples to support your opinion.",
    "answer": "There are some advantages of being able to cook. I have some reasons. Firstly, it is obvious that I can make healthy food. To keep myself healthy, I seriously care about my health. These days, people don’t have enough time to consider their physical health, and getting a lot of stress is another matter to think about. In my case, I try to cook at home, and take care of my health. Also, um~ I can save money. Let me tell you a story, because it will be more effective. A few days ago, I made pasta at home. I never used MSG. That’s it."
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "improve the gallery service",
    "answer": ""
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "building renovation",
    "answer": "put a big banner in front of the entrance / Customers will see it easly / send out text messages to regular customers"
  },
  {
    "tag": [],
    "question": "distributing tickets fairly",
    "answer": "You should do a raffle / Put everone's name cards into a box, and do a raffle / give tickets to employees who have kids"
  }
]